All the order today's regular meeting of the Mime and Special Utility Authority.
Item two is Invocation Band.
Do you do the honors please?
Certainly.
Your staff.
Dear Heavenly Father, as we gather here this evening,
we thank you very humbly for all the blessings that you have bestowed upon us here in our community and our state and our nation.
We pray that you grant all of these leaders wisdom and guidance,
so that the work that we do here will be pleasing in your sight.
We pray these things in the name of Jesus the Christ.
Amen.
I pray to the angels to the flag of the United States of America,
and to the great public for which it stands.
One nation under God, the indivisible with liberty and justice for all.
Thank you.
Item four is public input unscheduled personal territories.
The only answer was to address the authority on the idea agenda.
Item five is Constellant Gender Staff is recommending item six to nine for the Consent Agenda.
If there are no questions, we're going to obtain a motion to approve the Consent Agenda as recommended.
And the second.
Second.
We'll call please.
One.
All right.
Item ten is proposed to an issue of application agreement template for residential service
and authorize the trust manager or his designated execute.
That's got been and just named next to it.
Hi, Jim.
Well, we have revised the residential order agreement to supply utilities to the residents.
And this kind of asking matter.
We just want to make sure that you guys are for the tip of it because you are people that are contracting with the individuals for the service.
A couple of things I want to point out is that it does indicate of the Oklahoma State Session Firmary Foundation to collect online.
Is that contract?
And I'm going to point out specifically put that in there on the behalf of Good Judge Colour.
So we're incorporating that statute specifically into the contract.
Okay.
The dispatch ease and the call or text that we will do.
That it is by ordinance that we're kind of putting it on our people.
Okay.
So existing customers like myself is.
I don't sign that document.
I'm not going to be asked to sign a new agreement.
This is just for new customers going forward.
And so in any way to make that retroactive to existing customers.
Okay.
I mean, if I'm past do, I'm going to get a text.
But where is your voice?
Well, we really hadn't discussed that particular issue, but I just think it'd be so complicated
to figure out which ones we've done that with and which ones we haven't.
You know, for the most part, obviously relatively new customers may be ones that were at risk
of going into default, but for the long-standing customers, probably not a great risk
of them going into default.
Okay.
Any other questions on the recommended change in the contract between the MSUA and its customers?
But one other thing I wanted to point out or emphasize is that in acting this,
would be authorizing the city manager or his designate to actually sign this contract on the
part of the city.
We'd never actually done that.
The city has not actually signed it as a contract, which it would be beneficial for us to do
it that way.
But this is the one.
Yes.
And this is the product of several meetings with staff that are involved in this actual process.
To try to make sure we do everything as expeditious of a fashion as we can on their part
and still make it fair and reasonable to the customers.
Okay.
Any questions?
We have a motion to approve the MSUA application and agreement.
Can we make the motion?
Yes.
We're up all foot.
Question?
Yes.
My fourth term.
Johnson?
Sure.
Hi.
I'm 11 years new business and I give business.
I am 12 as trustee committee announcement in the announcement.
I am 13 as executive session pursuant to 25 or as 10 or 7, 17 for the purpose of conferring
on matters between economic development, including the transfer of property financing and the
administration of a proposal to entice the business.
So okay.
Within the jurisdiction of my annual special utility authority and just a little editorial
comment.
So the plan is that we have two executive sessions tonight.
One for the MSUA and one for the council.
So we're going to go into executive session.
Then we're going to recess.
Finish.
We're not going to join.
We're just going to recess.
And then we're going to move on to the council meeting.
Through those items.
Going to executive session.
That way we don't have to go upstairs.
One up and back one time.
So that's kind of the plan.
Do you have anything you need to add as our legal counsel for item 13?
No, I will have something to add.
When we do it for the second council.
So do we have a motion?
We've grown executive session for the reasons listed on there.